绿带的学员们  掌握龙之真气
Green belts, the path of the dragon
绝非易事
is not easy.
嘿呀
Hyah!
别给吓趴下了
Do not be scared.
这苍蝇还活着  勉强算吧
The fly lives, barely.
我这么做的目的是杀鸡儆猴
But only so he can warn his friends
三心二意是绝对不可饶恕的
that distractions will not be tolerated.
天啊  蕾·道伊老师可不是闹着玩的
Wow, Sensei Rae Dawn is no joke.
我听说如果你直视她的眼睛
I heard if you look directly in her eyes,
她就能偷走你的灵魂
she can steal your soul.
小龙帕克
Dragon Parker,
你准备好通过释放出
are you ready to advance from green belt
你内在的龙之真气
to blue belt
来表演飞龙跳跃后空踢
by unleashing your inner dragon
把你的绿带升级为蓝带了吗
and performing the leaping dragon back-kick?
准备好了 老师
Ready, Sensei.
嘿呀
Hyah!
很令人钦佩 年轻的小龙
Impressive, young dragon.
这是你的蓝腰带
Your belt.
提醒一下你们的父母 新腰带价值 9.95 美元
Remind your parents it's 9.95 for the new belt
你踢烂的靶子价值 1.2 美元
and 1.20 for the target you broke.
小龙埃文
Dragon Evan,
- 你准备好  - 你先等等再说
- are you ready... - Let me stop you right there.
我妈说我今天还不能释放龙之真气
My mom says I can't unleash my dragon today.
什么
Excuse me?
她觉得我不能参加一个
She thinks I shouldn't participate in an activity
以成败评判小孩子的活动
where kids are judged in terms of winning or failing.
尤其是我失败已经板上钉钉了
Especially when I'm going to fail.
总之我今天能通过
Anyway I can get a blue belt
敞开心扉来促膝长谈
by being open about my feelings
而拿到蓝带么
and talking out issues?
看起来你内在的小龙更像是冒牌的蜥蜴啊
Seems your inner dragon is more of a salamander.
想拿腰带  没门
No belt for you.
你有一周时间来努力拿到蓝腰带
You have one week to earn your blue belt
要么就忍辱负重的看着班里其他人
or endure the shame of watching the rest of the class
挪到周二 2 点半的那节课
move on to the 2:30 Tuesday slot
就除了你
without you.
我绝对不能就这么让老师
There was no way I was gonna let the sensei
拆开我们
break up the team of
极品武术双人组
super-awesome martial arts dude
和他挚爱的老哥们
and his beloved sidekick,
雀斑  和嬉皮笑脸的冒牌蜥蜴
freckles, the smiling salamander.
耶
Yeah.
埃文也许要换一个新绰号了
Evan might need a new nickname.